Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
I am a brawler by trade.
I show mercy to none...
...not even women!
Oiran...
...Knuckles!
Ah, how satisfying to strike you!
It must be because you're so big!
My, now...
Running out on me, are we?
Maricade!
The webs that barred your way...
...are flammable!
Mariarson!
"Over before it even began,"
you say?
In you came, like a knight in shining armor,
to cover for the shameful Black-Leg Sanji's disgrace,
but should you be
handily defeated here,
you will make a fool of yourself,
just as he did!
Bloom in this sea of flames,
if you dare!
Can flowers bloom
within flame?!
Oh, no!
She's the Demon Child!
We can't let her live!
Your crime? Existing!
As I told you before,
you're a burden to
your crewmates!
A tramp like you...
...is sought after by
the great movers of the world...
...only for that
Poneglyph-deciphering brain you possess!
Who needs your personality?
They just need you alive!
Nothing but means to an end!
You need neither
your arms, nor your legs!
Punching such
an irritating tramp...
...feels sooo good!
See, now? Your vulgar rampage
caused this raging inferno to spread!
What are you going to
do about it?
Going to ask that skeleton monster
to put it out again?
Go on, ask him to clean up
the mess you made!
I overheard you utter some
ridiculous things yourself, Black Maria-san.
Were I you...
I would flee from
where you stand!
Robin-san!
Hey, you listening?
I've been telling you...
...you've gotta know how
to throw a punch, just in case!
Is slapping
out of the question, Koala?
The people after you
want you dead, though!
Slapping won't cut it!
How about using the heel of your palm,
this part of it?
Speed matters more than power!
Throw with speed,
pull back with speed!
And be like, wham!
Huh?
Robin, want me to teach you
Dragon Claw Fist?
Would be a great
addition to your arsenal!
What're you doing here, Sabo-kun?!
I'm the one teaching her!
Doesn't matter
who teaches her, does it?
Then I will!
No, I'm gonna!
I'm more suited for it than you!
I'm a Fishman Karate assistant instructor!
Hey now, hey now... No need for
the both of you to impose!
Oh, Hack!
Robin's strong enough
with her locking techniques.
But once we've gone our separate ways,
we can't protect her!
I told you she's strong, didn't I?
But with Fishman Karate,
Robin-san can really put her skills to good use!
Dragon Claw Fist's
better suited for that!
Robin has her own way of fighting!
Palms can be used
without special abilities like yours!
Dragon Claw Fist is great for practical stuff,
I'm telling you!
Palms!
Neither of you
are listening to me!
Robin!
I still ain't heard it straight from you!
Tell me you wanna live!
Help me, Robin-chan!
Never did I think that I would
want to become stronger...
ooofor the sake of another.
You'll be just fine
if you leave it to me!
Then...
Huh?
Mind teaching me a little
about that "palm" thing?
Okay!
Are you sure about
teaching me this, though?
Of course we are!
You're important to us,
Robin-san!
This is...
...the ace up your sleeve!
It uses your palms as well...
...but it's a secret art of
Fishman Karate!
Mil Fleurs,
Fishman Karate:
Giganteum!
Where were you aiming?
Certainly...
Certainly, my palms came in handy
countless times.
Sense your opponent's core!
Sense my opponent's core!
Drat!
The flames are gone?!
What...?
That form...!
A demon!
Unhand me!
There are people
who truly need me,
and rely on me!
And for them,
I would go so far as to...
...become demon incarnate!
Gran Jacuzzi...
...Clutch!
Black Maria-sama is
at peak performance today!
That tramp is finished!
S...top...!
"Need neither arms nor legs"?
No! Not mine...!
I was talking about yours!
What... was that noise?!
Black Maria-sama!
The ice is in the way!
Damn that skeleton monster!
Black Maria... sama?
Black Maria-sama was...!
It's a demon!
Much obliged to you all
for lining up!
And now...
Phrase d'Armes:
Orchestra!
Welcome home...
Robin-san.
Glad to be home.
Thank you...
...for waiting
I'm a little... exhausted.
Whoa, there.
Robin-san...
You all actually get it, right?!
That's a month's worth of my food!
You'd better return the favor,
or there's gonna be problems!
Anyway, I can't believe
you had this much food on you!
My Swamp-Swamp Fruit power
is bottomless!
Straw Hat!
What's happened to our captain,
Bepo, and the rest?!
73!!
Iw aaiu"?
I am begging you!
Only you, Shinobu, are capable of this!
Indeed I am capable,
but why do you wish this?!
I would grant
Luffy his wish!
His wish?
I must take Luffy there!
That is why I wish to go
to Onigashima once again!
What?!
Why... do you speak
such ridiculousness?!
could never again let you
set foot upon such a dangerous place!
Wait, Shinobu!
If nothing is done, the Flower Capital
and the Land of Wano will be annihilated!
It is for that reason I must go,
no matter the cost!
I beg of you!
You must, for our sakes-
Momonosuke-sama,
listen to me very carefully.
If I do this,
you will never...
be able to return
to your current appearance!
That is to say,
your mind will remain that of a child...
...and only your body will mature!
If you follow through-
I care not!
I might be able to become...
...a bigger dragon that way!
And yet...
I cannot bring myself
to do such a thing...
Momonosuke-sama!
I am begging you!
Y-You mustn't do that,
Momonosuke-sama!
Please, Shinobu!
Use your Ripe-Ripe Jutsu...
to make me an adult...
Please...
make me an adult...
Make me an adult!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates,
numbering 30,000, versus...
the 5,400-strong
Samurai-Pirate Alliance raiders!
The gap in manpower quickly shrank...
...thanks to
O-Tama's Kibi Dango strategy,
...and the valiant fighting by
samurai and pirate alike.
The resolute, top-ranking enemy officers,
the Flying Six, are wiped out!
Onigashima, far above
the Wano mainland,
...will soon arrive
upon the Flower Capital!
Why did you serve Kurozumi Orochi,
that hideous man...
Fukurokuju?!
We ninja serve the reigning Shogun
to the bitter end.
Ninja Art: Clone Technique!
Such insolence!
What about the man you serve?!
A ghost, is he not?!
You speak of Oden-sama?!
The real one is there!
An emotionally-laden man like you...
...is completely incapable
of being a ninja!
No matter how adept you
are with ninja techniques!
It is thanks to our emotions...
that we are sated!
That day, we...
...cried together,
laughed together.
And together,
we died with Oden-sama!
We are but apparitions,
seeking to execute our lord's will!
You will not sully that
by calling it a mere "duty"!
It is because we servants
bear these emotions...
...that we have no qualms
if we should die in battle!
Today, the night called
Orochi-Kaido shall end,
and the brilliant sun
will rise in its place...
...with Momonosuke-sama
as Shogun!
Hawkins!
Just how many damn substitutes
do you have?!
I've only a handful left...
Ah, this doesn't look good for me...
I mourn those lives.
Bring it on, punk!
Only a few remain...
...however,
what truly matters is...
...whose lives are in them, yes?
Huh?!
The hell's with this
stab wound from outta nowhere?!
Hey, what's with you
all of a sudden?!
Don't tell me that straw doll...!
Now you notice...
It would have been entertaining to observe you
kill Kid without realizing that it's him...
...but watching you
grow helpless...
...is just as interesting,
wouldn't you say?
You can kill me...
...only after killing your own captain!
You damned, lousy...!
Oh, how delightful it is...
...to imagine you suffering
under that mask.
Go on, then...
Do your worst! I won't stop you!
You are one messed up guy,
ya know that?
Outta my way, Trafalgar!
The price of betrayal is high!
Hey there,
ex-Animal Kingdom Pirate garbage!
I'm sentencing
all o' ya to die in a fire!
Where's Marco-san?!
Do something, anything, please!
He's reached his physical limits!
It's up to us to do something!
Sangoro-san!
Are you okay?!
Dammit...
two at once is freakin' rough!
They're looking for Zorojuro!
What the hell's
Mossbrain doing?!
Does he need more time?
He was in critical condition
in the first place...
Chopper, Miyagi!
If the drug ain't working,
take that green mummy and get outta here!
Sanji...
We've already administered the shot!
Hang in there, Zoro!
Who can stop them?!
If nothing is done,
everyone on this floor is dead!
Find Roronoa Zoro...
...and choke the life out of him!
Seems they gave him
some strange treatment.
Don't let him recover!
Aye!
I'm right here!
Sangoro-san!
You little...!
I ain't letting you morons
do whatever you want!
Damned monsters...
The dust is so thick,
I can barely see!
I'm going to
remove Vinsmoke Sanji!
Mlem!
If you had married Pudding...
we wouldn't be stuck working
with those idiots!
It's him, Master!
I see...
Mlem!
Chew on this,
you Germa defect!
Come on ouuuut!
This un's for Pedro!
Ain't done with ye yet!
I found Roronoa Zoro!
Make him dead!
Aye!
They found us!
Protect Zorojuro!
He suffered these wounds honorably!
Aye!
They're all wounded!
Finish them off along with Roronoa!
Keep up with them!
Stay strong, Miyagi, Tristan!
Okay!
King's here!
Don't do it, sonny!
Dammit! Do I gotta do
everything for ya, Mossbrain?!
You ain't gettin' in our way,
Black Leg!
You're done!
Imperial Flame!
Undying Thistle!
I once heard...
A long, long time ago,
upon the red wall...
...dwelled a race of people
capable of igniting themselves.
King the Wildfire, huh?
How the hell're you still kickin'...
Marco?!
Go to hell already...
Whitebeard Pirates!
Sure...
I give!
I've gotten all I want outta this.
This is as far as I take things.
And now...
The real stars of this show, oh yeah.
Roronoa!
Diable...
Three-Sword Style:
Purgatory...
Mouton Mallet!
Way to go, Straw Hats!
It really did
heal his wounds!
Still...
I fear what comes after...
Hey, Swirly Brow.
Once we've won this fight...
Yeah, we're gonna get to see a little bit...
...Of Luffy...
...becoming the Pirate King!